{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":6066,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":9,"width":1024,"height":627,"responsive":true,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Button_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_3","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si8769","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si8859","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_33","roles":{}},{"id":"si8885","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si8783","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_6","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide4221","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Button_3","si8769","Button_4","si8859","Image_33","si8885","si8783","Image_6","Text_Caption_1"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3546},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4221"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_7","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si10052","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si10065","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_10","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si10115","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si10128","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_11","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si10166","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si10179","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_25","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_26","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_27","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide10197","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Button_9","si10052","si10065","Button_10","si10115","si10128","Button_11","si10166","si10179","Image_25","Image_26","Image_27"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":261},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10197"}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_9","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_13","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si10968","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si10981","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_22","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_23","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_14","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si11031","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si11044","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_24","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_15","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si11082","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si11095","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide11113","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Button_13","si10968","si10981","Image_22","Image_23","Button_14","si11031","si11044","Image_24","Button_15","si11082","si11095"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":261},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11113"}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_1","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_8","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_3","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_5","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_1","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Button_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Button_1","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8395","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8408","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_2","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Button_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Button_2","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8474","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8486","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_3","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Button_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Button_3","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8553","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8565","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide4379","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_8","Image_5","Text_Entry_Box_1","Text_Entry_Button_1","si8395","si8408","Text_Entry_Box_2","Text_Entry_Button_2","si8474","si8486","Text_Entry_Box_3","Text_Entry_Button_3","si8553","si8565"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4379"}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_4","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_14","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_8","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_20","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_14","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Button_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Button_14","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10732","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10744","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_15","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_16","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"Slide10884","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_14","Image_20","Text_Entry_Box_14","Text_Entry_Button_14","si10732","si10744","Text_Entry_Box_15","Text_Entry_Box_16"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10884"}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_2","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_9","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_4","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_7","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_4","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Button_4","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9031","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si9043","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_5","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_6","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"Slide9183","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_9","Image_7","Text_Entry_Box_4","Text_Entry_Button_4","si9031","si9043","Text_Entry_Box_5","Text_Entry_Box_6"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9183"}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_3","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_5","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_17","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Button_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Button_17","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11525","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11538","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_18","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Button_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Button_18","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11604","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11616","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_28","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide9485","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Entry_Box_17","Text_Entry_Button_17","si11525","si11538","Text_Entry_Box_18","Text_Entry_Button_18","si11604","si11616","Image_28"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":1548},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide9485"}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_5","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_10","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_31","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide11298","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_31"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11298"}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_6","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_11","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_32","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_32","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide11391","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_32"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11391"}}},{"id":"Pool421","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":421,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"PBL Individual","class":"project","title":"PBL Individual","children":["Slide4221","Slide10197","Slide11113","Slide4379","Slide10884","Slide9183","Slide9485","Slide11298","Slide11391"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":377,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":[],"minScore":0,"maxScore":0,"passScore":0}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"launch_content","SCCriteria":"launch_content","exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide4221","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide10197","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide11113","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide4379","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide10884","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide9183","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide9485","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide11298","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide11391","title":"Slide 9"}]}